carolinehirons.com 2016-06-12

# Caroline Hirons: Legal/Privacy Policy

**LEGAL STUFF**

**Advice**  
The views expressed on this site are the author's own and are provided for informational purposes only. The author makes no warranties about the suitability of any product or treatment referenced or reviewed here for any person other than herself and any reliance placed on these reviews or references by you is done so solely at your own risk. Nothing on this site shall be construed as providing dermatological, medical or other such advice and you are always advised to seek the advice of a suitable professional should you have any such concerns.  
**  
****Affiliates**  
Some links may be affiliates. This is new to me so I'm monitoring how it goes. It doesn't affect my opinion at all, but then I think regular readers will know that. ;)  
Any sponsored content prior to March 2016 is clearly labelled according to the ASA guidelines. As of March 2016 I am not accepting any sponsored posts.

**Product Recommendations Disclaimer**  
I am always happy to recommend products and this has obviously become a key part of the blog and now YouTube. Any recommendation is based on my experience with something - or the trusted experience of a tester - but everyone's skin is different and something that works for me may not necessarily work for you in the same way.  
The same with allergic reactions - it is impossible to anticipate allergies - it is pretty much possible for anyone to be allergic to anything.

**Adverts**  
Adverts placed on here are done so by MODE Media and I have no affiliation with the companies featured.  
To provide the best browsing experience, this site uses cookies and by visiting this site you are agreeing to the use of cookies. For more information on the EU e-Privacy Directive or how to disable cookies click here.

**  
****PRIVACY STATEMENT**

Your privacy is important to CarolineHirons.com. This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that CarolineHirons.com collects, and the ways in which we use that personal information.

**Credit**

This document was created using a Contractology template available at http://www.freenetlaw.com

**Personal information collection**

CarolineHirons.com may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:

 information about your use of this website  
 information that you provide using for the purpose of registering with the website  
 information that you provide for the purpose of subscribing to the website services

**Using personal information**

CarolineHirons.com may use your personal information to:

 enable your access to and use of the website services  
 publish information about you on the website – only with your prior approval

Where CarolineHirons.com discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement.

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, CarolineHirons.com may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.

**Securing your data**

CarolineHirons.com will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

CarolineHirons.com does not store  personal information you provide.

**Cross-border data transfers**

Information that CarolineHirons.com collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which CarolineHirons.com operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

[In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the internet and may be available around the world.]

You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.

**Updating this statement**

CarolineHirons.com may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website.

You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.

**Other websites**

This website contains links to other websites.

CarolineHirons.com is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.

**Notice Regarding Online Behavioral Advertising**  
We allow third party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our Web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g. click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice visit the NAI at http://www.networkadvertising.org.   
To opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit http://www.aboutads.info/choices. 

**Contact**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or CarolineHirons.com treatment of your personal information, please write:

 by email to google@carolinehirons.com
